[
  {
    "question": "Qui? (kee)",
    "answers": ["What?", "Who?", "When?", "Why?"],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Quoi? (kwah)",
    "answers": ["What?", "Who?", "When?", "Why?"],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Quand? (kohn)",
    "answers": ["What?", "Who?", "When?", "Why?"],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Où? (oo)",
    "answers": ["Where?", "Who?", "When?", "Why?"],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Pourquoi? (poor-kwah)",
    "answers": ["What?", "Who?", "When?", "Why?"],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Comment? (kom-mohn)",
    "answers": ["What?", "Who?", "How", "Why?"],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Combien? (kohm-bee-ahn)",
    "answers": ["How much?/How many?", "Which one?", "What is it? (casual)", "Why?"],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Lequel/Laquelle? (luh-kel/lah-kel)",
    "answers": ["How much?/How many?", "Which one?", "What is it? (casual)", "Why?"],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Quel/Quelle? (kel)",
    "answers": ["Which?/What?", "How much?/How many?", "When?", "What is it?"],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "C’est quoi? (say kwah)",
    "answers": ["What time is it?", "What is it? (casual)", "When?", "Which one?"],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Qu’est-ce que c’est? (kess-kuh say)",
    "answers": ["What is it? (standard)", "When?", "Which one?", "What time is it?"],
    "correctIndex": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Où sont les toilettes? (oo sohn lay twah-let)",
    "answers": ["Do you want to go to the toilet?", "Where are the restrooms?", "Are the restrooms closeby?", "Who wants to go to the toilet?"],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Quelle heure est-il? (kel uhr ay-teel)",
    "answers": ["When?", "Is it far?", "Can you help me?", "What time is it?"],
    "correctIndex": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Pouvez-vous m’aider? (poo-vay voo may-day)",
    "answers": ["When?", "Is it far?", "Can you help me?", "What time is it?"],
    "correctIndex": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "C’est loin? (say lwan)",
    "answers": ["When?", "Is it far?", "Can you help me?", "What time is it?"],
    "correctIndex": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "C’est près d’ici? (say pray dee-see)",
    "answers": ["How much?/How many?", "Can you help me?", "Is it near here?", "Is it far?"],
    "correctIndex": 2
  }
]
